YWCA of the U.S.A. Records. Record Group 1. General and History
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES V. BIOGRAPHICAL FILES
  - Cratty, Mabel
    - Death, Memorial tributes and services (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Endowment Fund (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Writings (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Cu (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Curtis, Fannie Holland (Mrs. A. Maurice) (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Cushman, Vera Scott
    - General (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, miscellaneous (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Cuthbert, Marion (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Da (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Dabb, Edith (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Dail, Hilda Lee (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - d'Alviella, Countess Helene Goblet (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Dammond, Ellen (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Davis, Helen Alling (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - De - Dil (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Derricotte, Juliette (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Dickinson, Sarah Truslow (Mrs. Robert L.) (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Dieson, Eldri (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Dingman, Mary A (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Dockstader, Harriet "Skip" (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Dodge, Grace Hoadley (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Dodge Family
    - General (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Huntington, Elizabeth Dodge (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Dodson, Dan (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Doherty, Gladys M. (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Doo-Dow (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Dow, Caroline Bell (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Dreier, Mary E. (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Droll, Hattie (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Du (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Dudley, Marion (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Dunham, Julia S. (Mrs. Edward W.) (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Dunham, Marcia O. (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Dunn, Mary Skinner (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Dutchess, Jeanette (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - E (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Earle, Mary Clayton (Mrs. Ralph) (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Eastman, Elizabeth (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Eckert, Bertha (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Elliott, Grace Loucks
    - General (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Memorial Correspondence (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Esgar, Mildred (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Espy, Lilian (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Ewing, Eloise (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Fa (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Farrell, Eileen (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Fasnacht, Kathryn (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Fauset, Crystal Bird (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Fe - Fi (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Ferebee, Dorothy (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Fidler, Edith Alverson (Mrs. Lon) (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Field, Jessie (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Fields, C. Virginia (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Finley, Martha Boyden (Mrs. John H.) (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Fisher, Welthy (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - Fl (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Fo (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Fr - Fz (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - French, Eleanor (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - French, Mary Billings (Mrs. John) (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Ga (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Gage, Frances (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Gaiser, Mary Cooper Jewett (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Galpin, Leta (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Gambrell, Sarah (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Garrison, Jane (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Gates, Edith (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Ge-Gh (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Gerlach, Tabitha (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Gerwick, Katherine (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Gi-Go (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Gibson, Henrietta (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Gilbert, Annie Kate (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Gilkey, Geraldine Brown (Mrs. Charles W.) (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Gra (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Graham, Abbie (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Graham, Jewel Freeman (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Gratz, Lois (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Graves, Elsa (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Gre-Gu (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Green, Margaret (Mrs. E.H.) (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Grenfell, Hilda (Mrs. Arthur) (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Guthrie, Anne (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Haa-Ham (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Hamilton, Florence D. (Mrs. Wallace) (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Hamilton, Grace Towns (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Hamilton, Madrid (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Han-Har (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Hanna, Sallie R. (Mrs. John M.) (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Harbison, Janet (Mrs. E. Harris) (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Harcourt, Edith Farley (Mrs. Clayton J.) (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Hardcastle, Jane (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Harper, Elsie (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Harrison, Agatha
    - General (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Annuity Fund, 1950 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence to Margaret Burton and Margaret Fuller, 1924-54 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Has-Hay (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Hawkes, Anna Rose (Mrs. Herbert E.) (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Haynes, Elizabeth Ross (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Hea - Hen (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Heard, Winifred (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Heckman, Miriam Sipfle (Mrs. Walter C.) (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Hedgeman, Anna Arnold (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Heim, Virginia (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Heineman, Irene Taylor (Mrs. Arthur S.) (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Hendee, Elizabeth
    - General (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - YWCA (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Photographs, Nationality Work (Box 39, Folder 8a)
    - Speeches and Writings
      - 1922-29 (Box 39, Folder 9)
      - 1932-33 (Box 39, Folder 10)
      - "The Economic Position of Women in the Nineteenth Century," M.A. Thesis, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Henshaw, Helen Manville (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Heo - Her (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Herring, Elizabeth (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Hes - Hev (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Hi (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Hickman, Emily (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Hill, Agnes Gale (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Hiller, Margaret (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Hillis, Ina Ruth (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Hirth, Emma (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Hitchcock, Elizabeth French (Mrs. Ethan Allen) (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Ho - Howard (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Howarth, Susan (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Hoy - Hum (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Hun-Hz (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Hunt, Bessie (Mrs. Fred Hunt) (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - I (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Ingraham, Mary
    - General (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Notes on Race Relations, 1942-52 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Jac - Jar (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Jackson, Alexine Clement (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Jaynes, Joyce M. (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Je - Ji (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Jo-Joh (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Job, Martha (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Johnson, Lydia (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Joi - Jz (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Jones, Marian (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Ka (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Kawai, Michi (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Ke - Kh (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Kenyon, Dorothy (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Khan, Ivy (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Ki (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Kl - Ky (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Knight, Margaret (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Knowles, Helen (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Kuhn, Margaret (Maggie) (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - La (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Lamborn, Elizabeth (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Lamont, Elizabeth Kinney (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Lea-Leo (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Ler-Li (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Lerrigo, Edith
    - General (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Speeches and Writings (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Ll- Lu (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Love, Susan (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Lowry, Genevieve (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Lucke, Elmina (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Lumpkin, Katharine DuPree (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Lundy, Mary Ann (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Ly (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Lyon, Sarah (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Ma-Map (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - MacArthur, Kathleen W. (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Macdonald, A. Caroline (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Macy, Edith Dewing (Mrs. Edward W.) (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Mains, Frances Helen (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Mar (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Markey, Dorothy Gary (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Marti, Elizatheth "Beth" (Mrs. Lloyd) (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Marsh, Bessie (Mrs. Leo B.) (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Marvel, Beth (Mrs. Archie D.) (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Mas-May (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Mathai-Davis, Prema (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Mayhew, Abby Shaw (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Mc (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - McAfee, (Martha) Jane (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - McCanse, Jessie Hill (Mrs. Ralph) (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - McCarthy, Louise Roblee (Mrs. Eugene Ross) (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - McClellan, Josephine N. (Mrs. William S.) (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - McClintock, Mabel Case (Mrs. H.H.) (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - McConnell, Dorothy Frances (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - McCombs, A. Parks (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - McCulloch, Rhoda (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - McFarland, Carmen (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - McWilliams, Marion Lerrigo (Mrs. William J.) (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Mea - Mi (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Mead, Ada Hardy (Mrs. Charles W.) (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Mead, Margaret P. (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Meares, Carrie (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Mercer, Marion (Mrs. C. Douglas) (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Miguel, Elisa (Mrs. M.C.) (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Miller, Bernice (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Miller, Elizabeth White (Mrs. Charles O.) (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Miller, Ethel Prince (Mrs. Kenneth D.) (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Mo (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Monroe, Edna A. (Mrs. Marshall) (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Moore, Elisabeth Luce (Mrs. Maurice T.) (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Morris, Alice Vanderbilt (Mrs. Dave Hennen)
    - General (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Scrapbook: notes and writings, 1902-21 (Box 43, Folder 14-15)
  - Morrison, Barrying (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Morriss, Margaret S. (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Morse, Rebecca Finley (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Morton, Helen (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Moser, Frances (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Mott, John R. and Leila (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Mu-My (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Muldowny, Ruth (Mrs. Sylvester) (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Munn, Frances (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Murphy, Betty Anne (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Muskrat, Ruth (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Musser, Elise (Mrs. Burton W.) (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Na - Nj (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Neely, Ann Elizabeth (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - No (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Norris, Elizabeth Downe (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - O-Ol (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Olcott, Katharine (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - On-Oz (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Osilaja, (Elizabeth) Folaremi (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Owen, Mildred
    - General (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - National Training School notebook, 1923-1924 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Term papers, 1923, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Owens, Sarale Alice (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Pa (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Packard, Mary Woody (Mrs. Arthur W.) (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Packard, Ruth L. (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Paist, Theresa Wilber (Mrs. Frederic M.) (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Palmer, Elizabeth (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Papes, Alice (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Park, Esther (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Parker, Katherine Blunt (Mrs. Edwin B.) (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Paul, Dorothea (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Pawlowski, Georgia M. (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Paxton, Jean Grigsby (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Pe (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Pell, Orlie (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Perry, Frances (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Perry, Sue (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Pfeutze, Louise (Mrs. Paul E.) (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Ph-Po (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Ping, Margaret Li-A (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Pole, Hilda (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Pu-Q (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Putnam, Glendora McIlwain (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Ra- Re (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Rainey, Mildred (Mrs. Homer) (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Reed, Clara (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Reynolds, Annie (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Reynolds, Dolores (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Ri (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Rice, Anna V. (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Rietveld, Harriet (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Risley, Florence (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Rob (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Roberts, Caroline D. (Mrs. Marshall O.) (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Robinson, Marion (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller family (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller, Abby Aldrich (Mrs. John D., Jr.)
    - General (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1918-29 (Box 46, Folder 5-8)
    - Writings (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Rockefeller, Mary French (Mrs. Laurance S.) (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Roe, Mildred S. (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Roelofs, Henrietta (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Rouse, Ruth (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Royden, A. Maude (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Ru-Ry (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Russell, Maud
    - General (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Inventory to papers at New York Public Library (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Russell, Valerie (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Sa (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Saddler, Juanita (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Savacool, Mildred (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Sc (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Schmidt, Irma (Mrs. George Paul) (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Schulte, Lucy (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Se (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Sh (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Sharon, Mary Bruce (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Sheley, Helen (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Shell, Helen H. (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Sherman, Opan Woodley (Mrs. Dallas B.) (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Shinn, Ruth (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Si-Sm (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Simms, Florence
    - General (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Florence Simms: A Biography by Richard Roberts (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Memorial Fund and Memorial Lecture at Smith College (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Writings and student notes (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Simons, Savilla Millis
    - General (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Speeches and Writings (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Sims, Mary (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Sims, Norma (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Skallerup, Nancy (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Smith, Alice O. (Mrs. Allan C.) (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Smith, Celestine Louise (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Smith, Myra (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Snyder, Ida Sloan (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - So (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Sokoloff, Nancy Boyd (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Southard, Helen (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Spa-Spe (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Spaulding, Pauline Snyder (Mrs. Sumner) (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Sparling, Edna (Mrs. E.M.) (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Spencer, Clarissa Hale (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Speer, Emma Bailey (Mrs. Robert
    - General (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Spellmann, Dorothea (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Spi-Sta (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Starr, Rhea (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Stauffer, Norma (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Ste-Stz (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Steele, Henrietta Diszeroth (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Stille, Sue (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Stringfellow, Wilma (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Stuff, Grace (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Su-Sy (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Ta-Te (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Takeuchi, Kikuye (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Taylor, Harriet (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Taylor, Hazel Stout (Mrs. Joseph) (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Terlin, Rose (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Terry, Eva (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Th-To (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Thoburn, Helen (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Thompson, Elizabeth Staplecamp (Mrs. Harry A.) (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Thurman, Sue Bailey (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Tillett, Gladys Avery (Mrs. Charles W.) (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Timmel, Sally Jane (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Townsend, Alice Greenough (Mrs. Edward M.) (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Toyer, Aurelia (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Tr-Tz (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Travers, Lillian K. (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Trecker, Harleigh B. (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Troiano, Rose (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Tucker, Katharine D. (Mrs. Henry H.) (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Turner, Ella (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Tyndall, Margaret (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - U (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - Va (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - Van Arsdale, May B. (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - Van Asch Van Wijck, Cornelia (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - Van Meter, Ruth (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - Vaughan, Katharine (Box 50, Folder 27)
  - Vawter, Dorothy Fuller (Mrs. William A.) (Box 50, Folder 28)
  - Ve-Vz (Box 50, Folder 29)
  - Volz, Verna (Box 50, Folder 30)
  - Wa (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Waddell, Catherine Hughes (Mrs. Chauncey L.) (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Walker, Helen M. (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Walker, Irene (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Walker, Katherine (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - We (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Webb, Nellie S. (Mrs. James A., Jr.) (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Weber, Eleanore (Mrs. Ford R.) (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Wellington, Beatrice M. (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Wh (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Wheeler, Clara Boyd (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Wheeler, Mary (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - White, Julia J. (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Wi-Will (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Wickenden, Elizabeth
    - General (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Speeches and Writings (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Wilcox, Elsie (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Willett, Mary Jane (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Williams, Frances Harriet (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Williams, Marjorie Brackett (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Williamson, Margaret (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Wils-Wiz (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Wilson, Carol Green (Mrs. George Osborn) (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Wilson, Doris V. (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Wilson, Elizabeth
    - General (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - The Road Ahead: Experiences in the Life of Frances C. Gage, The Womans Press, 1918 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Wilson, Gertrude (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Wilson, Jessie Woodrow (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Wilson, Katharine Lobdell (Mrs. William R.) (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Winn, Cordella (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Wo-Wr (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Wood, Mary E. (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Woodsmall, Ruth Frances (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Woolley, Mary E. (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Wright, Sara-Alyce P. (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Wu-Wy (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Wygal, Winnifred (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Y-Z (Box 52, Folder 17)
- SERIES VI. 'FOREIGN' YWCAS REFERENCE FILES
  - British-American YWCA of Paris, 1904-12 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - YWCA of Argentina, 1914, 1940 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - YWCA of Australia, 1955, 1959, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - YWCA of Belize, 1999 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - YWCA of Burma: photograph album, Taunggyi day care centre, 1961-62, [see also YWCA of India, Burma and Ceylon below] (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - YWCA of Canada
    - General, 1928-90 (Box 53, Folder 6-8)
    - Montreal: annual reports, 1877-78, 1940 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - YWCA of Ceylon, 1908-14, [see also YWCA of India, Burma, and Ceylon] (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - YWCA of China, [see separate boxes listed below]
  - YWCA of Denmark, 1942, 1994 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - YWCA of German: "The German National Committee and Its Work", 1910 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - YWCA of Ghana: "Youth and Youth Organizations in Ghana", 1973 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - YWCA of Great Britain
    - General, 1884-1998, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Go Forward: Monthly Journal for Secretaries and Workers, Feb, Apr-Dec 1892 (Box 54, Folder 6-7)
    - London
      - Annual Report, 1884-90 (Box 54, Folder 8-9)
      - Our Own Gazette, 1896-1901
        - Vol. XV-? (Box 54, Folder 10)
        - Vol. XVII-XVIII (Box 55, Folder 1-2)
  - YWCA of Hong Kong, 1991-92, [see also YWCA of China] (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - YWCA of India, Burma, and Ceylon
    - General, 1908-44, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Our Indian Magazine, Oct-Dec 1899 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - The Young Women of India,, 1900-01 (Box 55, Folder 6-7)
    - The Young Women of India and Ceylon, Sep 1914-May 1915, Apr- Jun 1916 (Box 55, Folder 8-10)
    - Woman's Outlook in India
      - Jul-Dec 1916 (Box 55, Folder 11)
      - Jan, Jun, Aug, Dec, 1917 (Box 56, Folder 1)
      - Jan-May 1918 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - YWCA of Italy, n.d. (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - YWCA of Japan
    - General, 1913-66, n.d. (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Photograph album, 1926-30 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - YWCA of Jordan, Christmas Crib Dolls, 1964, n.d. (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - YWCA of Kenya
    - General, 1987, n.d. (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Handbook for Volunteers and Staff Responsible for Administration of YWCA Hostels, compiled by Norma Stauffer, n.d. (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - YWCA of Korea
    - General, 1973-74, n.d. (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Scrapbook: Rural Training Centre, Tongnae, 1957 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - YWCA of Mexico: cookbook, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - YWCA of New Zealand: Auckland YWCA Peace Site scrapbook, 1987 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - YWCA of Singapore, 1914 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - YWCA of South Africa
    - General, 1908-09, 1986, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - The Quarterly Record, 1918-28 (incomplete) (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - YWCA of Thailand: Cook Book, Bangkok, 1967; Annual Report, 1995 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - YWCA of Uganda: First African Sub-Region Workshop, 1993 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - YWCA of Zambia, 1964-71, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - YWCA of China
    - General and History
      - General, 1914-79, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 1)
      - "Women in a Changing China: The YWCA" paper by Jean McCown, University of Michigan, 1971 Associations (Box 58, Folder 2)
        - Canton, 1913, 1932 (Box 58, Folder 3)
        - Chefoo, 1932, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 4)
        - Foochow, 1914 (Box 58, Folder 5)
        - Hong Kong, 1920, 1970 (Box 58, Folder 6)
        - Peking, 1980, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 7)
        - Shanghai
          - General, 1911-38 (Box 58, Folder 8)
          - Normal School of Hygiene and Physical Education, 1917-20 (Box 58, Folder 9)
        - Tientsin, 1935-43 (Box 58, Folder 10)
      - Scrapbook, circa 1932-34 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Biography, 1936, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Constitution and By-laws, 1933 (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Minutes and reports
      - National Committee of the YWCA of China and Executive Committee
        - 1919-26 (Box 58, Folder 14-19)
        - 1927-31, 1933 (Box 59, Folder 1-6)
      - Ad Interim Committee and Executive Committee, 1936-37 (Box 59, Folder 7-8)
      - Executive Committee, 1939, 1950 (Box 59, Folder 9)
      - Reports
        - Miscellaneous, 1927-49, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 10-11)
        - Annual, 1915-47 (Box 59, Folder 12-14)
      - "The YWCA in China", 1922 (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - Conferences, 1908-40 (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - Conventions, 1923, 1928, 1933 (Box 60, Folder 1-3)
    - Financial, 1919-47, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Industrial Work
      - General, 1906-41, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 5)
      - Studies, 1928-31 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - International Education Commission, 1940, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Legal issues, 1937-43 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Literature Project Commission, 1933 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Publications
      - Miscellaneous, 1914-41, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 10)
      - News Items, 1918-19 (Box 60, Folder 11)
      - The YWCA Magazine, 1923-25 (Box 60, Folder 12)
      - The Green Year: The YWCA Magazine, 1923-35 (Box 60, Folder 13)
      - The 'Green Year' Supplement
        - 1925-27 (Box 60, Folder 14-16)
        - 1928-33 (Box 61, Folder 1-4)
      - News letters, 1927-33 (Box 61, Folder 5)
      - Songbooks, 1923-25 (Box 61, Folder 6)
      - Study courses, 1921, 1923 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Publicity, 1939-40 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Reference materials, 1922-50, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 9-10)
    - Rural Work
      - General, 1932, 1935, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 11)
      - Photograph album, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 12)
      - Reports, 1928-39 (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Student Work, 1921-27, 1934 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Student Relief Committee, 1939-40 (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Photograph albums: Grace Steinbeck, n.d.; Mary Elizabeth Durfee, Nanking YWCA, 1918-19; Abby Mayhew, 1913-21 (Box 62, Folder 1-3)
      - Florence Pierce [Secretary in Peking (1925-27) Tientsin (1927-33); Executive Director, Mukden Association (1934-37), worked primarily with students]
        - General, 1974 (Box 63, Folder 1)
        - Miscellaneous, 1926-62, n.d. (Box 63, Folder 2)
        - Correspondence, 1931-35, 1949-50 (Box 63, Folder 3)
        - Writings, 1933, n.d. (Box 63, Folder 4)
        - Photograph albums (Box 63)
          - "Minor Pilgrimages and Peking Scenes", 1929 (Box 63)
          - Tientsin YWCA activities (Box 63)
          - China and Korea, 1925-27 (Box 64)
- SERIES VII. WORLD'S YWCA REFERENCE FILES
  - General and History
    - General, 1908-99, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 1-2)
    - Historical publications
      - General, 1920s-40s, 1994 (Box 65, Folder 3-6)
      - National Associations
        - 1926-40 (Box 65, Folder 7)
        - 1947, 1955 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - General pamphlets, 1938-2000, n.d. (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Constitution and policy statements (incomplete), 1934-95 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Constitution re-drafting, 1953-54 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Statements of Policy, 1963, 1994 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Annual Reports (incomplete)
    - 1896-1920 (Box 66, Folder 6)